A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Middle East and Africa, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia Field Office Files, Office Files of Wesley Edwards FA644
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1960-1976 (Bulk: 1972-1976); bulk; I
  - Educational Television -- Ministry of Education -- Instructional TV, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
  - Educational Television -- Wade Media Report and Ford Foundation Evaluation of Educational TV Project in Saudi Arabia, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Educational Testing, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - English Language -- Ministry of Education and "Preliminary Assessment of Training Needs for Instructional and Instruction-Related Personnel" (1/2), 1968-1975 (Box 2)
  - English Language -- Ministry of Education and "Preliminary Assessment of Training Needs for Instructional and Instruction-Related Personnel" (2/2, second copy), 1968-1975 (Box 2)
  - Environment, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Florida State Proposal Re: Educational Curriculum, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Foreign Affairs, Ministry of -- Correspondence and Ford Foundation Reports, Data, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence -- Incoming and Outgoing, 1973-1974 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence and Reports -- Summer 1974 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence (1/2), 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - General Correspondence (2/2), 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Gulf Area -- General Information and Correspondence Re: Ford Foundation Activities and Possible Projects, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Health, Ministry of -- General Information, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Indiana University -- Audio/Visual -- Re: Educational Technology Center for Saudi Arabia, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Individual Awards Manual -- Policies and Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Individual Awards -- Grants Manual, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Literacy Education -- Ministry of Education and World Bank, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Management Information System, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Management Information System -- Institute of Public Administration -- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Manpower Planning -- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Manpower Planning -- Reports, Incl. "Toward an Appropriate Strategy for Training Skilled and Unskilled Workers", 1974 (Box 2)
  - Memos -- Ford Foundation Interoffice, May-Dec 1974 (Box 3)
  - Memos -- Ford Foundation Interoffice -- General and Miscellaneous, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Memos -- Ford Foundation Interoffice, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Memos -- Ford Foundation Interoffice (primarily Ford Foundation administrative policies and Foundation Initiatives - not Saudi Arabia specific), 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Middle Eastern Projects -- Reports, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Natural History -- Iran, Yemen, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Project Correspondence -- Incoming and Outgoing, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Project Notes, Comments, Reports, General Information Memos -- Ministry of Education, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Public Administration Review, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Research -- International Economic Order -- Worldwide Competition Announcement, Feb 1, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Riyad (Riyadh), University of -- Graduate Program, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Riyad (Riyadh), University of -- Library Project, 1970-1975 (Box 3)
  - Riyad (Riyadh), University of -- Library Project -- General Correspondence and Information, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Sara, Nathir -- Educational Districts in Saudi Arabia, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Saudi Arabia Program Notes -- Incl. Memo Re: Staff Meeting and Visit by Mr. and Mrs. Bell, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Saudi Foundations, 1970-1974 (Box 3)
  - Saudi Translation Program, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - School Principal Training Project -- Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Science Education -- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Science Education -- General Information and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Social Sciences -- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Social Sciences -- General Information, Correspondence Incl. Ford Foundation Report on Science and Technology in Society, 1972-1976 (Box 3)
  - Staff Meetings -- Memos, 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Staff Meeting (January 27-28, 1975), Jan 27-28, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Staff Meetings -- Cairo Meeting -- Materials, Jun 1975 (Box 3)
  - Television -- General Information Re: Television in Saudi Arabia, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - World Bank -- Correspondence and Reports Re: Education and Training, 1974-1975 (Box 3)